https://www.bikesomewhere.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BikeSomeWhere is committed to respecting the privacy rights of website visitors. The following policy describes how we collect, protect and use information we receive from website visitors.
What information do we collect?
How do we use your information?
How do we protect visitor information?
Do we use "cookies"?
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
How can you opt-out, remove, or modify information that you have provided to us?
Third Party Links
Changes to Our Policy
Questions and Feedback
Terms and Conditions
Your Consent
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, date of birth, e-mail address, mailing address, daytime phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously or purchase without registering.
For security purposes, we are not saving your credit card number on our servers, however, the credit card processing company we use does.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
We also receive and store click-stream data and other information about visits to our websites. This information is used to analyze and improve the website experience.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive BikeSomeWhere e-mail, we may send you periodic e-mails from BikeSomeWhere. If you would no longer like to receive BikeSomeWhere e-mail, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?"section below. If you have not opted-in to receive BikeSomeWhere e-mail, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are pieces of information that a site sends to your computer while you are viewing the site. Cookies work in combination with content within the site itself to capture and remember information. For instance, cookies are used to remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to track your activity and understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity. This enables us to provide you with services or to improve your site experience. We also use cookies to provide us with aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third party service providers to assist us in serving cookies, however, they are not permitted to use the information collected except to help BikeSomeWhere conduct and improve its business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient -- like the features mentioned above -- and some of our services will not function properly.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting BikeSomeWhere's business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information in aggregate form may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions or completely opt-out of receiving BikeSomeWhere e-mail please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "Your Account" section.
To delete all of your BikeSomeWhere online account information from our database, please contact us. Please include your first name, last name, phone number and e-mail address email. Note that if you request your account information to be deleted from our database, we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on July 1, 2011.
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
This site is operated by BikeSomeWhere LLC.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
×
OK
Join our newsletter
Email Address
